

About

Nationality: Sudanese Date of birth: 2000-02-08 Address: Khartoum, Sudan

Meticulous web developer with a proven track record in creating remarkable and responsive solutions in the least possible time. Have 3+ years of experience in crafting and testing user-friendly interfaces, debugging and updating existing projects, and ensuring customer satisfaction. Looking forward to demonstrating my proven abilities in optimizing web functionalities in a challenging and motivating work environment.

Languages

- Arabic Native
- English fluent

YOUSIF AHMED

WFB DFVFI OPFR

Experience

Frontend Webdeveloper

Markon CS | 2020 - Present

- -Worked effectively in a team of four web coders to develop end-to-end web app development and saw client projects through their full lifecycle, thus ensuring 100% on-time delivery and working within clients' budgets
- -Collaborated with the senior web developer to clean up processes and boost performance.

Freelancer

|2021 - Present

- -Fixed bugs in existing websites and assisted clients in fixing problems in their website functions.
- -Consulted clients to determine their product specifications throughout the development process, increasing customer satisfaction and reducing rework costs

Education

Mechanical Engineering Bachelor degree
 University of Khartoum, Khartoum | 2016 - Present
 Description of the education/course.

Skills

- · Web development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Frameworks like Angular CLI, ReactJS
- ASP .Net core
- Mobile development with Android Studio
- GIT, Github
- Paython, C#, Kotlin

Contact

- ★ Khartoum, Sudan
- **L** +249 124682031